# 185 Patchwork Corners Poteet, TX 78065 210-501-9271 paulvera1988@yahoo.com

### SUMMARY

Effective and creative Web Developer with over 5 years of industry, and education setting experience. Dedicated to exceeding standards and taking on new challenges. Looking to help increase quantifiable leads and online presence by creating quality webbased content.

# EXPERIENCE

- Information Technology Teacher SWISD; Von Ormy, TX 2021 to Present
- Creative Designer (Part-time Contractor) Codeup LLC; San Antonio, TX 2021 to 2021
- Web Design & 2D/3D Animation Teacher New Braunfels ISD; New Braunfels, TX 2017 to 2021
- **Digital Content Creator VERAfied Creations; San Antonio, TX** 2018 to 2020
- Marketing Videographer & Content Creator Breakaway Practice LLC; San Antonio, TX 2016 to 2017
- Military Police 31B **United States Army** 2009 to 2014

### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- NODE.JS
- **JQUERY**
- **BOOTSTRAP 5**
- SQL
- **PYTHON**
- JSON

- FIGMA
- API
- VECTOR ART
- ADOBE SUITE
- WORDPRESS
- GIT
- **BASH**
- MS OFFICE SUITE
- **GOOGLE ANALYTICS**
- MAC OS / WINDOWS

# EDUCATION

- Full-Stack Development Certification University of Texas at Austin - Exp. April 2022
- Bachelor of Fine Arts Digital Video Production The Art Institute of San Antonio - 2017

I github.com/paul88vera